Guide to the Collection title
Collection title
2000-2005
EAD-TEST-002
1 linear_feet 1 box
Abstract test
General
test general
Scope and Contents Note
S and C test
Access Note
Collection is open for research.
Arrangement Note
Arrangement test
Acquisition Note
Acq test
Biographical Note
Bio test
Related Materials
Related test
- Series One Title
  General
  test general
  Scope and Contents Note
  S and C test
  Access Note
  TEST ACCESS
  Arrangement Note
  Arrangement test
  Acquisition Note
  Acq test
  Biographical Note
  Bio test
  Related Materials
  Related test
  - Subseries One Title
    Collection is open for research.
    - File One A Title, 2000 (Box 01, Folder 01)
    - File One A Title, 2000 (Box 01, Folder 01)
    - File One A Title, 2001-2003 (Box 01, Folder 02)
- Series Two Title
  - Subseries Two A Title
    - File Two A Title, 2004; 5 cubic_feet 5 rolls (Roll 02)
    - File Two A Title, 2005 (Roll 02)
  - Subseries Two Title
    - Subseries Two B ONE
      - File One B One Title, 2004 June 30 (Oversized box 03)
      - File One B Two Title, 2005 (Oversized box 03)
    - Subseries Two B TWO
      - File Two B Two One, 2004 June 30 (Oversized box 03)
      - File Two B Two Title, 2005 (Oversized box 03)
        - File inside File, 2005 (Oversized box 03)
    - File Two B Title, 2004 June 30 (Oversized box 03)
    - File Two B Title, 2005 (Oversized box 03)
- Top level file, 2005 (Oversized box 03)